Guide to the Dick Thornburgh Papers, 1932- AIS.1998.30.18
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Dick Thornburgh Papers, Series XVIII. Photographs
1932-2004
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Thornburgh, Dick
AIS.1998.30.18
6000 items
The Dick Thornburgh collection consists of 6000 photographs, approximately 500 of which are available online. Some are black and white, some color, and sizes vary. There are some photos by professionals and Pennsylvania's Commonwealth Media staff. Other snapshots are of a more informal nature, provided by event attendees and friends as well as by staff. The photographs date from Thornburgh's early childhood and continue into 2004. Many are from Thornburgh's two terms as Governor of Pennsylvania, and his years as Attorney General of the United States. Others are from his campaigns for U.S. Congress in 1966, his two gubernatorial campaigns in 1978 and 1982, and his campaign for U.S. Senate in 1991. Some are from events, others from foreign trips from his years as Governor, Attorney General, and his ongoing career. They are colorful, representative of a broad array of events and topics. Digital reproductions of portions of the collection are available online.
Access Restrictions
No restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Dick Thornburgh, February 27, 1998.
Previous Citation
Dick Thornburgh Papers, 1932-, AIS.1998.30, Archives Service Center, University of Pittsburgh
Pennsylvania -- Politics and government -- 1951-; Political campaigns -- Pennsylvania; Personal papers; Government; Women; Politics; Education; Social action; Environment; Thornburgh, Dick; Pennsylvania. Governor (1979-1987: Thornburgh); United States. Attorney-General; United States. Congress. Senate -- Elections; United States. Congress. House -- Elections; Pennsylvania. Governor -- Elections; Thornburgh family -- Photographs; Thornburgh, Ginny (Judson)
- Photographs, 1932-2004; XVIII.
  Scope and Contents note
  The Dick Thornburgh archive includes 6,000 photographs. Some are black and white, some color, and sizes vary. There are some photos by professionals and Commonwealth Media staff. There are other snapshots of a more informal nature, provided by event attendees and friends as well as by staff. The photographs date from Thornburgh's early childhood and schooling and continue into 2004, during his ongoing career. Many are from Thornburgh's two terms as Governor of Pennsylvania, and his years Attorney General of the United States. Others are from his campaigns for U.S. Congress in 1966, his two gubernatorial campaigns in 1978 and 1982, and his campaign for U.S. Senate in 1991. Some are from events, others are from trips abroad during his years as Governor, Attorney General, and his ongoing career. They are colorful, representative of a broad array of events and topics, and pictorially interesting.
  A major group of approximately 500 photographs for which we have ownership and/or permission have been digitized, are available here online, and are searchable.
  - Youth, Education, and Family Photographs, 1.
    - Thornburghs Parents (14), undated (Box 1500, Folder 1)
    - Infancy and Early Childhood (13), 1932-1945 (Box 1500, Folder 2)
    - Carnegie High School (1), 1946 (Box 1500, Folder 3)
    - Mercersburg Academy (10), 1946-1950 (Box 1500, Folder 4)
    - Yale University (2), 1950-1954 (Box 1500, Folder 5)
    - University of Pittsburgh School of Law, 1954-1957 (Box 1500, Folder 6)
    - Virginia Hooton Thornburgh (20), 1949-1960 (Box 1500, Folder 7)
    - John and David Thornburgh, Infants (3), 1957-1960 (Box 1500, Folder 8)
    - Virginia Judson Thornburgh (10), 1940-1960's (Box 1500, Folder 9)
    - Dick and Ginny Judson Thornburgh, Wedding, 1963 (Box 1500, Folder 10)
    - Dick and Ginny Thornburgh with Bicycle (3), February 14, 1979 (Box 1500, Folder 11)
    - Peter Thornburgh with National Association for Retarded Citizens (5), October, 1974 (Box 1500, Folder 12)
    - Thornburgh Visit to Aberdeen Proving Ground (11), 1975 (Box 1500, Folder 13)
    - John Thornburgh's Graduation from Bucknell University (1), June 3, 1979 (Box 1500, Folder 14)
    - David Thornburgh's Graduation from Haverford College (1), 1981 (Box 1500, Folder 15)
    - Virginia Judson's (Grammy) 80th Birthday (4), January 9, 1982 (Box 1500, Folder 16)
    - John and Sharon Thornburgh's Wedding (2), May 1, 1982 (Box 1500, Folder 17)
    - John and Sharon Thornburgh (3), undated (Box 1501, Folder 1)
    - John, Sharon, and Kendall Thornburgh (1), undated (Box 1501, Folder 2)
    - Kendall Thornburgh (2), undated (Box 1501, Folder 3)
    - David Thornburgh and Becky McKillip (1), undated (Box 1501, Folder 4)
    - David and Becky McKillip Thornburgh's Wedding (2), August 25, 1985 (Box 1501, Folder 5)
    - Four Generations: Ginny, Sharon and Kendall Thornburgh and Virginia Judson (1), October, 1984 (Box 1501, Folder 6)
    - Peter Thornburgh with the Colonial Park Group Home at the Governor's Office (16), December, 1984 (Box 1501, Folder 7)
    - Dick Thornburgh with Kendall Thornburgh (2), December, 1984 (Box 1501, Folder 8)
    - 1985 Family of the Year Award given by the Pennsylvania Association for Retarded Citizens (1) (Box 1501, Folder 9)
    - Dick and Bill Thornburgh, undated (Box 1501, Folder 10)
    - Dick and Ginny Thornburgh with Virginia Judson (2), undated (Box 1501, Folder 11)
    - Dick and Ginny Thornburgh with Ann Thornburgh (1), undated (Box 1501, Folder 12)
    - Dick Thornburgh with Siblings and their families (13), undated (Box 1501, Folder 13)
    - Family Reunion (1), undated (Box 1501, Folder 14)
    - Thornburgh Family Portraits (9), 1966-1977 (Box 1501, Folder 15)
    - Thornburgh Family Portraits (5), 1977 (Box 1501, Folder 16)
    - Thornburgh Family Portraits (5), 1979 (Box 1501, Folder 17)
    - Thornburgh Family Portrait (4), 1980-1997 (Box 1501, Folder 18)
    - Thornburgh Family Portrait (1), 2001 (Box 1501, Folder 19)
  - Early Law Career, Community Work, and Political Activities, 2.
    - Junior Bar Association with Raymond Burr and David Tuthill (1), 1963 (Box 1502, Folder 1)
    - Allegheny Lawyer (1), 1965 (Box 1502, Folder 2)
    - Shafer for Governor (3), 1966 (Box 1502, Folder 3)
    - Ray Bliss, John Volpe, Joe Durzo, and Al Capozzi (1), 1967 (Box 1502, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller for President (10), 1968 (Box 1502, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller for President (8), 1968 (Box 1502, Folder 6)
    - Young Lawyers/Pennsylvania Bar (1), 1970 (Box 1502, Folder 7)
    - County Federation of Women's Clubs, Washington, PA (2), 1970 (Box 1502, Folder 8)
    - Home for Crippled Children Fundraising Campaign (2), 1967 (Box 1502, Folder 9)
    - Thornburgh's Award Ceremonies and Civic Activities (20) (Box 1502, Folder 10)
    - Virginia Thornburgh (2) (Box 1502, Folder 11)
    - Award Ceremonies for Virginia Thornburgh (8) (Box 1502, Folder 12)
  - Campaign for United States Congress, 1966; 3.
    - Thornburgh With Petitions to Run for Congress in 1966 (Box 1502, Folder 13)
    - Campaign Brochure Photos (5), 1966 (Box 1502, Folder 14)
    - Formal Photograph (1), 1966 (Box 1502, Folder 15)
    - Painting the 10th Ward Headquarters in Pittsburgh (8), 1966 (Box 1502, Folder 16)
    - Star Car (2), 1966 (Box 1502, Folder 17)
    - Campaigning (14), 1966 (Box 1502, Folder 18)
    - Dick Thornburgh Will Stir Things Up In Congress, 1966 (Box 1502, Folder 19)
    - Campaign Rally (2), April 13, 1966 (Box 1502, Folder 20)
    - Opening of Campaign Office (10), September 12, 1966 (Box 1502, Folder 21)
    - Opening of Campaign Office (9), September 12, 1966 (Box 1502, Folder 22)
    - Thornburgh's Campaign Office, 1966 (Box 1502, Folder 23)
    - Election Eve (1), 1966 (Box 1502, Folder 24)
  - Constitutional Convention, 1967-1968; 4.
    - Pennsylvania Constitutional Convention (2), 1967-1968 (Box 1503, Folder 1)
  - United States Attorney for Western Pennsylvania, 1969-1975; 5.
    - Professional Photographs (4), 1969-1975 (Box 1503, Folder 2)
    - United States Attorney Photographs (6), 1969-1975 (Box 1503, Folder 3)
    - United States Attorney Staff Photos (6), 1969-1975 (Box 1503, Folder 4)
    - Federal Attorneys, Department of Justice (2), 1969-1975 (Box 1503, Folder 5)
    - Counterfeit Haul (1), October, 1969 (Box 1503, Folder 6)
    - Drug Haul from an International Narcotics Ring, Undated (Box 1503, Folder 7)
    - Justice Commission on Crime and Delinquency (4), 1971-1972 (Box 1503, Folder 8)
    - President Richard Nixon with United States Attorneys, 1972 (Box 1503, Folder 9)
    - John Scully and Thornburgh, 1972 (Box 1503, Folder 10)
    - Japanese Friendship Tour for Community Leaders (24), December, 1972 (Box 1503, Folder 11)
    - Japanese Friendship Tour for Community Leaders Photograph Album (105), December, 1972 (Box 1503, Folder 12)
    - Pollution Bounty Checks, circa 1972 (Box 1503, Folder 13)
    - Mazzei Case (3), 1974 (Box 1503, Folder 14)
    - Tony Grosso (1), circa 1975 (Box 1503, Folder 15)
    - Tony Grosso Court Case Drawings (4), 1969-1975 (Box 1503, Folder 16)
    - Thornburgh with Pennsylvania Supreme Court Justices, 1969-1975 (Box 1503, Folder 17)
  - Assistant Attorney General, 1975-1977; 6.
    - Interview with Thornburgh When Appointed AAG (2), 1975 (Box 1504, Folder 1)
    - Assistant AG Swearing-In Ceremony (8), July 9, 1975 (Box 1504, Folder 2)
    - Professional Photographs (2), 1975-1977 (Box 1504, Folder 3)
    - AAG Office and Staff (4), 1975-1977 (Box 1504, Folder 4)
    - Philadelphia Bar Association (1), March 11, 1976 (Box 1504, Folder 5)
    - Washington and Jefferson College, LLD Honorary Degree (6), May 29, 1976 (Box 1504, Folder 6)
    - Department of Justice Hierarchy with Attorney General Levi, c. 1976 (Box 1504, Folder 7)
    - Pennsylvania State Police (5), c. 1976 (Box 1504, Folder 8)
    - Drug Enforcement Agency, New Orleans (3), c. 1976 (Box 1504, Folder 9)
    - Thornburgh Signing Executive Agreement regarding Law Enforcement cooperation with the Italian Government (5), c 1976 (Box 1504, Folder 10)
    - Thornburgh Signing Executive Agreement regarding Law Enforcement cooperation with Japan (4), c 1976 (Box 1504, Folder 11)
    - United States Department of Justice Picnics (9), 1975-1977 (Box 1504, Folder 12)
    - AAG Photos (2), 1975-1977 (Box 1504, Folder 13)
  - Campaign for Governor, 1978; 7.
    - Reagan Dinner, June 9, 1977 (Box 1504, Folder 14)
    - Campaign Fundraiser, September, 1977 (Box 1504, Folder 15)
    - Dick Thornburgh in Philadelphia, Fall, 1977 (Box 1504, Folder 16)
    - Dick and Ginny Thornburgh (3), Fall, 1977 (Box 1504, Folder 17)
    - Brochure Photo (5), 1977 (Box 1504, Folder 18)
    - Campaign Event (4), October 4, 1977 (Box 1504, Folder 19)
    - Beaver County Chapter of the National Association of Accountants, October 14, 1977 (Box 1504, Folder 20)
    - "On the Farm" with Penrose Hallowell (4), Winter, 1977 (Box 1504, Folder 21)
    - Dick and Ginny Thornburgh (1), January 10, 1978 (Box 1504, Folder 22)
    - Fundraising Dinner (1), February 10, 1978 (Box 1504, Folder 23)
    - Ribbon Cutting Ceremony with Commissioner Bill Davis at the Opening of the Westmoreland County Headquarters (14), February 28, 1978 (Box 1504, Folder 24)
    - Primary Debate (1), April, 1978 (Box 1504, Folder 25)
    - Campaign Visit (1), April 21, 1978 (Box 1504, Folder 26)
    - Republican Rally with John Heinz, Allegheny County (15), May 12, 1978 (Box 1504, Folder 27)
    - Brunch in Harrisburg (8), May, 1978 (Box 1504, Folder 28)
    - Campaign Trail (2), June, 1978 (Box 1504, Folder 29)
    - Schaeffer 500 at Pocono Downs (11), June 25, 1978 (Box 1504, Folder 30)
    - PA Republican Heritage Group, Philadelphia (1), July 8, 1978 (Box 1504, Folder 31)
    - Campaigning in Bucks County (6), Summer, 1978 (Box 1504, Folder 32)
    - Softball Game (1), Summer, 1978 (Box 1504, Folder 33)
    - Frank Morrow Farm, Beaver County (17), August, 1978 (Box 1504, Folder 34)
    - Thornburgh riding horse at campaign event (2), August, 1978 (Box 1504, Folder 35)
    - Siegfried Weis, President of Weis Markets, Inc (1), August 16, 1978 (Box 1504, Folder 36)
    - On the Capitol Steps (1), September 20, 1978 (Box 1504, Folder 37)
    - Scranton, William (6), Fall, 1978 (Box 1504, Folder 38)
    - GOP Ethnic Event, Fall, 1978 (Box 1504, Folder 39)
    - Campaign Office, Pittsburgh (8), Fall, 1978 (Box 1504, Folder 40)
    - Campaign Event (2), Fall, 1978 (Box 1504, Folder 41)
    - Visit with Gay Pendleton (1), Fall, 1978 (Box 1504, Folder 42)
    - Parade (2), Fall, 1978 (Box 1504, Folder 43)
    - Meeting People (13), Fall, 1978 (Box 1504, Folder 44)
    - Montgomery County Court House Hierarchy (1), Fall, 1978 (Box 1504, Folder 45)
    - Brenneman Farm (1), October 26, 1978 (Box 1504, Folder 46)
    - GOP Rally, Armstrong County (5), October 27, 1978 (Box 1504, Folder 47)
    - General Electric Plant Tour with Plant Manager Pete Lubin (5), October 31, 1978 (Box 1504, Folder 48)
    - Campaign Photograph with David, Ginny, and John Thornburgh (1), 1977-1978 (Box 1504, Folder 49)
    - Campaign Photos (10), 1977-1978 (Box 1504, Folder 50)
    - Campaign Photos (9), 1977-1978 (Box 1504, Folder 51)
    - Governor Elect and Family (6), 1978 (Box 1505, Folder 1)
    - Moving into the Governor's Home, January, 1979 (Box 1505, Folder 2)
    - Inaugural Portrait (2), January 1979 (Box 1505, Folder 3)
    - Inauguration Day, 1979 (Book), January 15-16, 1979 (Box 1505, Folder 4)
    - Inaugural Events, 1979 (14), January 15, 1979 (Box 1505, Folder 5)
    - Inaugural Ceremony, 1979 (13), January 16, 1979 (Box 1505, Folder 6)
    - Inaugural Ceremony, 1979 (13), January 16, 1979 (Box 1505, Folder 7)
    - After the Ceremony (4), January 16, 1979 (Box 1505, Folder 8)
    - Inaugural Ball (16), January 16, 1979 (Box 1505, Folder 9)
  - Re-election Campaign, 1982; 8.
    - 1982 Reelection Campaign (11) (Box 1505, Folder 10)
    - Campaign Dinner (2), undated (Box 1505, Folder 11)
    - Election Night, Philadelphia, November 2, 1982 (Box 1505, Folder 12)
    - Governor Thornburgh Committee Members (1), December, 1982 (Box 1505, Folder 13)
    - 1983 Inaugural Ceremony (9), January 18, 1983 (Box 1505, Folder 14)
    - Inaugural Ball, January 18, 1983 (Box 1505, Folder 15)
  - Governor of Pennsylvania, 1979-1987; 9.
    - Events and People
      - AARP/NRTA Administrative Headquarters Dedication Ceremony, Fort Washington, PA, July 27, 1981 (Box 1505, Folder 16)
      - AEL Industries, Inc. (3), August 11, 1986 (Box 1505, Folder 17)
      - AMSCO, Erie, PA (3), undated (Box 1505, Folder 18)
      - Abad, Bernadine (1), August 13, 1981 (Box 1505, Folder 19)
      - Abington High School, Harrisburg (4), April 22, 1986 (Box 1505, Folder 20)
      - Advanced Technology Centers Press Conference, Philadelphia (1), April 26, 1983 (Box 1505, Folder 21)
      - African Trip, 1986 (Box 1505, Folder 22)
      - Agriculture Logo (1), January 11, 1981 (Box 1505, Folder 23)
      - Agriculture Progress Day, GOP Barbeque, Centre County (4), August 22, 1979 (Box 1505, Folder 24)
      - Alcott, Amy, Lady Keystone Open (6), July 1, 1984 (Box 1505, Folder 25)
      - Alexander, Governor and Mrs. Lamar, Nashville, TN (22), April 4-5, 1981 (Box 1505, Folder 26)
      - Allegheny Valley Expressway Ribbon Cutting (4), August 8, 1985 (Box 1505, Folder 27)
      - Allentown and Sacred Heart Hospital Center with Congressman Don Ritter and Secretary Arnold Muller (6), October 29, 1982 (Box 1505, Folder 28)
      - Allied Services Dedication, Joseph McDade Apartments, Scranton, PA (13), October 19, 1979 (Box 1505, Folder 29)
      - American Legion, Department of Pennsylvania (5), July 11, 1985 (Box 1505, Folder 30)
      - American Robot (2), undated (Box 1505, Folder 31)
      - American Scientific Center, Philadelphia, PA (11), January 25, 1984 (Box 1505, Folder 32)
      - American Water Works Association with Representative Paul Wass (6), June 22, 1982 (Box 1506, Folder 1)
      - Amish Farm Visit (11), 1979 (Box 1506, Folder 2)
      - Anderson, Marion, June 8, 1982 (Box 1506, Folder 3)
      - Antonovich, Mike, Los Angeles County Board of Supervisors, Los Angeles, CA (1), April, 1983 (Box 1506, Folder 4)
      - Army National Guard's 328th Aviation Company, $7.6 Million Aviation Support Facility, undated (Box 1506, Folder 5)
      - Aspen Institute, West Berlin, Germany (1), 1985 (Box 1506, Folder 6)
      - Art Opening for the New Directions Sculpture Exhibit, Governor's Home, Harrisburg (4), August 11, 1984 (Box 1506, Folder 7)
      - Bainbridge Street Bridge Opening (2), November 24, 1986 (Box 1506, Folder 8)
      - Baker, Senator Howard at the Pennsylvania Chamber of Commerce Dinner (4), October 28, 1985 (Box 1506, Folder 9)
      - Bank Hapoalim B.M., Philadelphia Branch (8), April 24, 1980 (Box 1506, Folder 10)
      - Baran, Walter, Secretary of General Services (4), 1979-1986 (Box 1506, Folder 11)
      - Baran, Secretary Walter and Irene at the 74th Annual Governors' Association, Afton, Oklahoma (1), August, 1982 (Box 1506, Folder 12)
      - Baran, Secretary Walter at Annual Cabinet Picnics, Frackville, PA (11), 1980-1984 (Box 1506, Folder 13)
      - Barr, Mayor Joseph, Funeral at Pittsburgh, PA (2), August 30, 1982 (Box 1506, Folder 14)
      - Bartle, Attorney General Harvey, Commissioner Ron Marks, and Commissioner Ann Goolsby (1), undated (Box 1506, Folder 15)
      - Bayfront Mini-Mall, Tour of the Construction Site, Erie, PA (4), October 23, 1981 (Box 1506, Folder 16)
      - Be Kind to Animals Week Proclamation Signing with Erik Hendrik, Executive Director of PA Society for Prevention of Cruelty to Animals (5), April 19, 1983 (Box 1506, Folder 17)
      - Bedford Village Walking Tour (5), July 16, 1981 (Box 1506, Folder 18)
      - Berger, Chief Justice Warren, U.S. Supreme Court Historical Society, Washington D.C. (5), May 6, 1983 (Box 1506, Folder 19)
      - Bethlehem Steel Corporation Illegal Steel Imports Rally, October 8, 1982 (Box 1506, Folder 20)
      - Biester, Attorney General Pete: Swearing-In Ceremony, Harrisburg, PA (1), February 16, 1979 (Box 1506, Folder 21)
      - Bill Signings (47), 1979-1986 (Box 1506, Folder 22-27)
      - Bio-Ecology Institute, Penn State University (2), August 9, 1985 (Box 1506, Folder 28)
      - Blood Donation, Harrisburg Hospital (2), January 22, 1986 (Box 1506, Folder 29)
      - Bloomsburg State College (4), October 11, 1979 (Box 1506, Folder 30)
      - Bluford, Lt. Col. Guy, Distinguished Service Medal Luncheon, Harrisburg, PA (12), May 18, 1984 (Box 1506, Folder 31)
      - Bohemia Grove Encampment, Monte Rio, CA, July 10-13, 1986 (Box 1506, Folder 32)
      - Bolton Mansion Haunted House 91), October 1978 (Box 1506, Folder 33)
      - Bradshaw, Terry [Pittsburgh Steelers Quarterback] (2), undated (Box 1506, Folder 34)
      - Brazilian Rotary Exchange Team (1), undated (Box 1506, Folder 35)
      - Brown, Barbara (1), January 7, 1987 (Box 1506, Folder 36)
      - Bucknell University Commencement (John K. Thornburgh's Graduation with Gov. Thornburgh Speaking) (3), June 3, 1979 (Box 1506, Folder 37)
      - 1979-1980 Budget Presentation (10), February, 1985 (Box 1506, Folder 38)
      - 1979-1980 Budget Signing, July 4, 1979 (Box 1507, Folder 1)
      - 1985-1986 Budget Preview (1) (Box 1507, Folder 2)
      - 1985-1986 Budget Address (14), February 5, 1985 (Box 1507, Folder 3)
      - 1986-1987 Budget Presentation and Bill Signing (3), February 4, 1986 (Box 1507, Folder 4)
      - Budget and Legislative Briefing, Harrisburg, PA (2), 1981 (Box 1507, Folder 5)
      - Burns, Ed, Bucks County, PA, undated (Box 1507, Folder 6)
      - Burton Elementary School, Erie, PA (1), May 10, 1984 (Box 1507, Folder 7)
      - Bush, Vice President George at the Governor's Home (8), October, 1980 (Box 1507, Folder 8)
      - Bush, Vice President George and Thornburgh (1), May, 1981 (Box 1507, Folder 9)
      - Bush, Vice President George with Governor and Ginny Thornburgh (1), July, 1983 (Box 1507, Folder 10)
      - Bush, Vice President George with Governor Thornburgh (1), February, 1984 (Box 1507, Folder 11)
      - Bush, Vice President George in Pennsylvania (6), May, 1984 (Box 1507, Folder 12)
      - Bush, Vice President George at National Governors Association in Washington, DC (5), February 24, 1986 (Box 1507, Folder 13)
      - Byrne, Governor Brendan Meets with Thornburgh in New Jersey (3), 1980 (Box 1507, Folder 14)
      - Byron, Leo, Department of Public Welfare Employee who was Held Hostage in TWA Hijacking) (7), 1985? (Box 1507, Folder 15)
      - Byron, Father William, Service of Rededication at Peace Church (1), January 16, 1981 (Box 1507, Folder 16)
      - Waldman photo 1979 and Cabinet Swear-In (3) (Box 1507, Folder 17)
      - 1986 Cabinet (3) (Box 1507, Folder 18)
      - Installation of Alexander Calder's Sculpture at the Governor's Home, Harrisburg, PA (5), September 12, 1980 (Box 1507, Folder 19)
      - Caliguiri, Mayor Richard (7), undated (Box 1507, Folder 20)
      - Capitol Tree Lighting Ceremony with Bryan Chubb (1), December 20, 1979 (Box 1507, Folder 21)
      - Capitol Tree Lighting Ceremony with Jacob Joehl (14), December 15, 1982 (Box 1507, Folder 22)
      - Carlisle High School AAAA State Championship Basketball Team, Ceremony, Harrisburg (4), April 1, 1986 (Box 1507, Folder 23)
      - Carnegie Mellon University/Department of Defense Soft Ware Productivity Center Groundbreaking, Pittsburgh, PA (2), September 11, 1985 (Box 1507, Folder 24)
      - Carpenters District Council of Western PA/Headquarters Building Ribbon Cutting Ceremony, Pittsburgh, PA (4), December 10, 1982 (Box 1507, Folder 25)
      - Carpenters Hall Rededication, Philadelphia, PA (7), June 24, 1979 (Box 1507, Folder 26)
      - Carstens, President Karl, Federal Republic of West Germany, Philadelphia, PA (10), October 6, 1983 (Box 1507, Folder 27)
      - Carter, President Jimmy at State Dinner (1), February 27, 1979 (Box 1507, Folder 28)
      - Carter, President Jimmy, undated (Box 1507, Folder 29)
      - Casey, Robert E. (3) (Box 1507, Folder 30)
      - Cervi, Pat, 5.5 Million Dollar Lotto Winner (1), April 8, 1983 (Box 1507, Folder 31)
      - Chang, T.T., Philadelphia, PA (1), undated (Box 1507, Folder 32)
      - Charleroi Junior-Senior High School Band (1), May 2, 1983 (Box 1507, Folder 33)
      - Charleroi-Monessen Bridge Ribbon Cutting Ceremony (6), December 20, 1985 (Box 1507, Folder 34)
      - Charles of the Ritz Dedication Ceremony, Monroe County (1), October 20, 1983 (Box 1507, Folder 35)
      - Charlie, The First Dog of Pennsylvania (4), undated (Box 1507, Folder 36)
      - Charter Day (1), March, 1981 (Box 1507, Folder 37)
      - Chesapeake Bay Meeting with Lee Thomas, Senator John Werner, Governor Harry Hughes, William Ruckelshaus, Senator Paul Sarbanes, and Governor Charles Robb (1), undated (Box 1507, Folder 38)
      - Children (18), 1979-1986 (Box 1507, Folder 39)
      - Chinese Cultural Center, Philadelphia (1), March 18, 1982 (Box 1507, Folder 40)
      - Clark, Dick (4), April 1, 1986 (Box 1507, Folder 41)
      - Clinton County CLIME Report, Harrisburg (4), October, 1980 (Box 1507, Folder 42)
      - Coal and Steel Rally, Ligonier, PA (8), undated (Box 1507, Folder 43)
      - Coalition of Northeast Governors (CONEG), Mount Washington, NH (3), undated (Box 1507, Folder 44)
      - Coalition of Northeast Governors (CONEG), Providence, RI (1), October 27, 1979 (Box 1507, Folder 45)
      - College Misericordia, Dallas, TX (10), May 3, 1980 (Box 1507, Folder 46)
      - Combs, William, Philadelphia PA (9), June 17, 1982 (Box 1507, Folder 47)
      - Commencements (7), 1979-1986 (Box 1508, Folder 1)
      - Commonwealth of PA, Washington Office (1), 1985 (Box 1508, Folder 2)
      - Community Affairs Check Presentation for Downtown Revitalization, Williamsport, PA (1), June 11, 1982 (Box 1508, Folder 3)